greasespot.net 2013-06-01

# Greasespot: Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Greasemonkey collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the Greasemonkey Application. This privacy policy applies to the Application and all products and services offered by Greasemonkey.  
  
Personal identification information  
  
We do not collect personal identification information from Users.  
  
Non-personal identification information  
  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Application. Non-personal identification information may include the list and/or number of installed scripts, the source they were obtained from, metrics describing usage of the Application and User behavior and Telemetry, and other similar information.  
  
How we use collected information  
  
Greasemonkey may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  

  * To improve our ApplicationWe may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.
  * UpdatesWe may use stored information in order to check for and/or install updates.
  * SynchronizationWe may share collected information for the purpose of synchronization across devices, via the standard Firefox Sync feature.

How we protect your information  
  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information and data stored on our Site.  
  
Sensitive and private data exchange between the Application and its Site happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.  
  
Sharing your personal information  
  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.  We may publish aggregated statistics based on this information online.  
  
Changes to this privacy policy  
  
Greasemonkey has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.  
  
Your acceptance of these terms  
  
By using this Application, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Application. Your continued use of the Application following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.  
  
Contacting us  
  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
Greasemonkey  
  
This document was last updated on November 7, 2012.
